<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on My corner</title>
        <link>https://arturorv7.github.io/mycorner/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on My corner</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:09:52 -0600</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://arturorv7.github.io/mycorner/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>The History of Testing In Software Systems</title>
            <link>https://arturorv7.github.io/mycorner/posts/examplepost/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:09:52 -0600</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://arturorv7.github.io/mycorner/posts/examplepost/</guid>
            <description>It&amp;rsquo;s hard to talk about the history of software, and about software and programming in general, without at least touching on the subject of testing. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to think about coding even a very simple program without including some sort of test in the process. This has been the case for a long time, probably for as long as I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing code. From making sure that my scripts would not cause my asset-flipped ROBLOX game to implode, to stressing over the several cases my professors could use to break my program after I turn it in.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s hard to talk about the history of software, and about software and programming in general, without at least touching on the subject of testing. In fact, it&rsquo;s hard for me to think about coding even a very simple program without including some sort of test in the process. This has been the case for a long time, probably for as long as I&rsquo;ve been writing code. From making sure that my scripts would not cause my asset-flipped ROBLOX game to implode, to stressing over the several cases my professors could use to break my program after I turn it in. Obviously, in these cases, the stakes are much lower than they would be for a piece of software intended for commercial use. While not testing my code could lead to me getting a low grade on an assignment, the developers of a program meant to provide an important service or store the sensitive data of its users can&rsquo;t afford the luxury of shipping an untested, or not properly tested, product.</p>


<video width = 100% controls>
  <source src = "/videos/SoftwareTesting.mp4" type = "video/mp4">
  Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>


]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
