<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on My corner</title>
        <link>https://arturorv7.github.io/mycorner/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on My corner</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:09:52 -0600</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://arturorv7.github.io/mycorner/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>The History of Testing In Software Systems</title>
            <link>https://arturorv7.github.io/mycorner/posts/examplepost/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:09:52 -0600</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://arturorv7.github.io/mycorner/posts/examplepost/</guid>
            <description>My name is Arturo Ramos Viedas, and I wrote this blog post as part of an assignment for my TC2007B course.
It&amp;rsquo;s hard to talk about the history of software, and about software and programming in general, without at least touching on the subject of testing. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to think about coding even a very simple program without including some sort of test in the process. This has been the case for a long time, probably for as long as I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing code.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My name is Arturo Ramos Viedas, and I wrote this blog post as part of an assignment for my TC2007B course.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s hard to talk about the history of software, and about software and programming in general, without at least touching on the subject of testing. In fact, it&rsquo;s hard for me to think about coding even a very simple program without including some sort of test in the process. This has been the case for a long time, probably for as long as I&rsquo;ve been writing code. From making sure that my scripts would not cause my asset-flipped ROBLOX game to implode, to stressing over the several cases my professors could use to break my program after I turn it in. Obviously, in these cases, the stakes are much lower than they would be for a piece of software intended for commercial use. While not testing my code could lead to me getting a low grade on an assignment, the developers of a program meant to provide an important service or store the sensitive data of its users can&rsquo;t afford the luxury of shipping an untested, or not properly tested, product.</p>

<div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
  <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EwK2Msg3FLI" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video"></iframe>
</div>

<p>This is a short but interesting video that summarizes the history and the importance of software testing pretty well. I&rsquo;d recommend watching the whole video, but the first three or so minutes get the point across just fine, in my opinion. I also liked the short segment &ldquo;Testing is an investment&rdquo; about four minutes into the video. I think this phrase is also good at summarizing the importance of testing in software systems, as the cost and time investment involved in software testing can sometimes cause us to cut corners, despite the potential future drawbacks.</p>
<p>It could be said that both software and software testing were born together. In 1950, the same year that a computer scientist known as Tom Kilburn wrote the first piece of software using machine code, the Turing Test was introduced as well. Ever since then, several testing techniques have been introduced to keep up with the ramping speed and efficiency of software and software development. Just a year later, Joseph Juran wrote about the importance of software testing and quality assurance in his book &ldquo;Quality Control Handbook.&rdquo;</p>
<p><img src="/images/software_automation.png" alt="book cover"></p>
<p>The first book on software automation, &ldquo;Software Test Automation: Effective Use of Test Execution Tools,&rdquo; would be written nearly 50 years later by Mark Fewster and Dorothy Graham. This marked a turning point in the gradual evolution of software testing. Throughout history, software testing has steadily evolved from manual methods and processes to automated and refined methods and practices that have become industry standards. Testing is now just as important as the actual development of software itself. In an ever-changing world where software errors can have unimaginable consequences, it is more important than ever to do everything to ensure the quality, reliability, and security of software.</p>
<p><strong>References</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://dogq.io/blog/a-brief-history-of-software-testing/">https://dogq.io/blog/a-brief-history-of-software-testing/</a>
<a href="https://www.geeksforgeeks.org/history-of-software-testing/">https://www.geeksforgeeks.org/history-of-software-testing/</a>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EwK2Msg3FLI&amp;ab_channel=VersaTest">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EwK2Msg3FLI&amp;ab_channel=VersaTest</a></p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
